atavi.com 2019-06-06

# Atavi - bookmark manager

The service is provided by SOFTLAB CORP.LLP (hereinafter referred to as "We", "Our", in any case and number, "SOFTLAB CORP.LLP "), registered at the following address: LAS SUITE 5 PERCY STREET, FITZROVIA, LONDON, ENGLAND, W1T 1DG; Legal entity registration number: OC392736. 

Atavi.com is committed to protecting your personal information when you are using Atavi services. 

This Privacy Policy covers Atavi's treatment of personally identifiable and other information that Atavi collects and receives, including information related to your past use of Atavi services. “Data” and “information” includes information about you that is personally identifiable, like your email address, and that is not otherwise publicly available. Where applicable we explicitly point out the use of personally identifiable data within our privacy policies. All other data is anonymous to us or is used pseudonymously. 

##  What information do we collect and how do we use it? 

To use the Atavi.com service in full you have to sign up for an Atavi.com account. When you do, we'll ask for personal information such as your email address. We may use such information to contact you to respond to a request from you, or in connection with legal proceedings, or if there has been a violation of our Terms of Service or this Privacy Policy. 

We collect and store in our server logs non-personally identifiable information, including but not limited to browser type, IP address, operating system, date and time of visits, pages visited on the site, time spent viewing the site, and return visits to the site. We also use Google Analytics, a service that records non-personally identifiable data such as browser type, operating system, the date and time of a visit, where visitors came from, the pages visited on this website, the time spent viewing site, where visitors went when they left the site, and return visits to the site. 

We aggregate this non-personally identifiable data to better understand how visitors use our site, and to help manage, maintain, and report on the use of our website. We store IP addresses for fraud detection and prevention purposes. 

##  Cookies, Double-Click, Web Beacons 

Atavi.com along with third-party vendors, including Google, use first-party cookies (such as the Google Analytics cookie) and third-party cookies (such as the DoubleClick cookie) together to inform, optimize, and serve ads based on your past visits to our website. 

Atavi.com uses web beacons to access our cookies inside and outside our network of websites and in connection with Atavi products and services. 

If you would like to remove our cookies from your computer, you can delete them using your browser (consult your browser's "help" menu to learn how to delete cookies). You may opt out of the use of the DoubleClick cookie for interest-based advertising by visiting Ads Settings. You may opt out of a third-party vendor's use of cookies for interest based advertising by visiting aboutads.info. 

##  Information that we share 

Atavi.com does not share your Personal Information with third parties for their marketing purposes. Atavi.com may share non-personally identifiable information, such as aggregate user statistics and Usage Information with third parties, including third party advertisers, content providers, and analytics providers, and may collect such information when you visit the Site. 

##  Changes to this Privacy Policy 

If there are any changes to this privacy policy, we will replace this page with an updated version. It is therefore in your own interest to check the "Privacy Policy" page any time you access our website so as to be aware of any changes which may occur from time to time. 

Please contact us with any questions about this website Privacy Policy: support@atavi.com 

##  _Cookies:_

A cookie is a small text file that is stored on a user's computer for recordkeeping purposes. Cookies can be either session cookies or persistent cookies. A session cookie expires when you close your browser and is used to make it easier for you to navigate our website. A persistent cookie remains on your hard drive for an extended period of time. 

##  _Web Beacons:_

Web beacons (also known as "pixel tags", "clear gifs", or "1x1 GIFs") are tiny graphics with a unique identifier, similar in function to cookies, and are used to track the online movements of web users or to access cookies. 

Web beacons may be invisible to you, but any electronic image or other web programming code inserted into a web page or email can act as a web beacon. Web beacons or similar technologies may be used for a number of purposes, including, without limitation, to count visitors to the Sites, to monitor how users navigate the Sites, to count how many emails that were sent were actually opened or to determine whether content sent was actually viewed. 

##  Last modified: September 2014 

← Back to main page
